What is going on, guys? Like you saw, we
moved our fifth wheel forward. We're
about to pick up a Caterpillar 340 and
we have to flip the axle. So, let's go
ahead and put the trailer down, hook up
my hydraulic lines, and get that axle
ready.
Hydraulic lines are connected.
Give it more throttle.
This switch push in operates the neck.
Pull out operates the flip axle. Neck
flip axle.
So, we're going to come back and now we
have hydraulic flowing to the rear axle.
Here's our lever.
Lower down.
Now that the axle is down,
I got to secure with the pins. We have a
air switch for that, which is right
here. Locking pin.
Push it in.
Our fourth axle is locked.
We're going to open the lines.
So, I have air. Come back here.
Connect our electrical.
That's it.
And then manually
we can adjust the air here as you see.
All right. Now, I'm going to lower the
entire thing.
Turn on my strobe lights.
I'm going to turn these strobe lights
off.
Let's go ahead and drop the trailer and
the third axle, too.
And that's it. I got the trailer set up,
ready to go. Third axle is down. Fourth
axle is down.
And uh once I load up and everything, I
raise this up. I'm going to start adding
air and match it to the fourth axle. We
have the gauge here.
I just put down the neck support so we
and pull forward now.
Heat. Heat.
Thank you.
Heat.
There's a 340. Sits perfectly
right here on the hammer plate.
Plenty of room right there.
Hey,
hold on.
Heat.
I got everything hooked up on the neck.
I'm going to go ahead now and raise the
airbags on the truck, lower the pusher
axle, and raise the trainer, too.
Let's go ahead and raise up the rear.
Now,
I'm going to set the PSI back here at
50 and then we'll check it here in a
bit.
I'm going leave it like that for now.
Let's go ahead and start chaining up and
then we'll check on these gauges
once I'm done with that. I don't have my
outrigger boards yet, so the track half
of it is outside. It's hanging a little
low, but it'll be fine. We'll be all
right. We still got plenty of it on the
deck itself. I bought this bar to clean
up the tracks where I'm going to put the
chain.
Heat. Heat.
Escavator's tied down to the deck.
Pressure gauge on the fourth axle. We're
about 43 PSI.
Now, let's check the rest of the
trailer. We're sitting at 60. So, we got
to come up on the fourth axle
to 60 PSI.
60 PSI there.
60 PSI here.
So, we're good to go. Right here in the
back.
Bought this oversized sign. I had a QT.
Did two holes on the mud flap. Secured
it with some zip ties. So, that worked
out perfectly.
Once again,
61 PSI.
60 PSI.
That's good to ride. We're going to do
two flags on the rear and two in the
front of the deck.
Right now, I'm just securing the excess
chain
like this for example
so it's not hanging.
There's unit 95 stretched out. We got
the 340 on the deck. Push her down.
Two tie downs on each corner of the
tracks.
One grabbing each trackpad. So you got
two track pads. I've seen people chain
from the same trackpad. I don't like
doing that. I like doing two different
trackpads. Top trackpad, bottom one.
Flags
all over.
This track is sagging a little bit, but
it'll be fine. Got a flag here. Same
thing over here. Secured from both track
pads.
Chain to get the boom.
60 PSI.
More flags. Oversized banner. Strobes.
Same thing here.
And we're on the
third setting.
So, we're not that low to the ground. We
have enough space.
But let's go ahead and get rolling. Got
to get rolling. Let me show you guys the
inside the pressure on the pusher axle.
Got the air suspension at 90 PSI, which
is roughly what it should be at. And the
pusher I have it at 40 PSI.
Heat up here.
Heat.
Heat up
Heat
up
here.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Heat
up
Heat. Heat.
Heat
up
here.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
made it to the delivery address. The
truck pulled flawlessly as you guys can
see.
Can't even tell there's a 340 behind
you. Heat.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
340 has been delivered.
What do you guys think about the
trailer? I know on the previous video we
just moved the dozer, didn't flip the
fourth axle,
but um I think it's amazing. I love this
trailer. The guys from Troy's Trailers
really knocked it out. If you guys are
already doing heavy haul and you've been
thinking about upgrading, looking for a
four axle, three axle, even a two with a
third flip, call my guys at Choice
Trailers. Phone number is right there on
the mud flap 21395800.
And link to my store also will be in the
description below. Shopg Trucking. You
can get some cool gear just like the hat
I'm wearing and plenty more others
available.
Look at that, man. Looks so good. 4x is
on the ground like that. Let's go ahead
and uh hook up the neck so we can get
out of here.
Heat up here.
Heat.
Heat
up
here.
Fourth axle has been flipped.
Very easy, man. I freaking love it.
Airbags are going up. Third axle is
going up, too. So, we're back to short
mode. Two on the ground.
[music]
Have to close.
the glad hands and disconnect
electrical line.
That way when I'm going down the road
and I'm pressing the brake or turn
signal, these aren't working.
Jack.
Hey. Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.